Tang Wei Xun +65 8768 3698

w31.xun.tang@gmail.com

Singapore Citizen

SUMMARY

IT Professional with 4+ years of experience in development web, batch and solution for diverse industry clients. Highly instrumental in all phases of the SDLC. Keen on continuous learning to take on exciting challenges. Passionate with development to built solution out of ideas.

EXPERIENCE

Full Stack Developer

07/2021 - 12/2021

Singapore Airlines

- Created and assisted with the development of 2 official websites using JavaScript, Java, React, CSS.
 - https://www.singaporeair.com/flight-schedule
 - https://www.singaporeair.com/express-booking
- Is there an action verb to describe this? Don't need to include prior to covid19, the experience is valid, before or after covid 19
- Had the opportunity to work on VTL changes.
- Debugged and implemented stipulation given by product owner.
- Leveraged on git bucket for version control and attended scrum ceremonies daily to ensure project delivery in the allocated time.

Software Engineer Associate

07/2018 - 10/2020

Accenture

- Applied technical expertise to build, test and deploy based on specification issued by functional team.
- Designed, developed, troubleshot, debugged, tested, ensured browser compatibility, implemented website code by using Java, Spring MVC and maven.
- Unit test methods utilizing Java to ensure quality of functionality.
- Conducted investigation on issues raised by users and implemented resolutions.
- Worked closely with Team Leads on change request functions.

Software Engineer New Associate

08/2016 - 06/2018

Accenture

- Showcased new software changes to product owners.
- Conducted investigation on issues raised by users and implement resolutions.
- Developed applications utilizing maven in Java (Spring & Hibernate) project.
- Utilized docu-sign API to digitally sign documents programmatically.

Android Developer (Internship)

04/2016 - 08/2015

ST Electronics

Singapore

- Collaborated with ST Electronics for requirements & translated into specifications for the development team.
- Collaborated with supervisor for new initiatives & in charge of the overall technical solutioning.
- Identified areas to improve in terms of productivity, propose, design solution, prototype & implement.

EDUCATION	
Temasek Polytechnic	07/2021 – 12/2021
Singapore	
 Industry Attachment (SGUP-CT – Microsoft Junior Full-Stack Developer) 	
Temasek Polytechnic	03/2021 - 06/2021
Singapore	
 Junior Full Stack Developer Bootcamp 	
Temasek Polytechnic	01/2016 - 01/2017
Singapore	
 Specialist Diploma in Smart Solution 	
Temasek Polytechnic	01/2014 - 01/2016
Singapore	
 Diploma in Info-Comm Network Engineering 	
Institute of Technical Education	01/2009 – 01/2010

Nitec in Info-Comm Network Engineering

COMPUTER SKILLS

Languages

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, BootStrap.

Java (Spring, Maven, Hibernate)

Software

Database: Oracle MySQL

Repository: Git

Platforms: Microsoft Windows 10, Linux Lubuntu

LINKS

GITHUB: https://github.com/weixuntang

LINKEDIN: https://www.linkedin.com/in/tang-wei-xun-8b4044136/